drivekool.com 2015-11-12

# Privacy & Terms|Drivekool

#### Important Points

  1. Drivekool is only a driving school agent. It does not operate driving services of its own. In order to provide a comprehensive choice of driving school operators, training times and prices to students, it has tied up with many driving school operators.

Drivekool advice to students is to choose driving school operators they are aware of and whose service they are comfortable with.

**PAYMENTS POLICY:**   

    * Drivekool.com is reselling driving training slots online to you. Hereby you authorize drivekool or drivekool.com to charge your card/bank account an amount as shown on your booking.
    * Your card details will be processed by our 128 bit secured payment gateway. You can pay with MasterCard, Visa, Debit Cards, Credit card or Net Banking 
    * You can also pay by cash directly to drivekool or to our affiliate driving school but we advise you to pay to drivekool directly so that we can control the quality of services for you.
    * Without payment drivekool or its affiliate shall not start your services. 
**REFUNDS POLICY:**   

    * Any cancellations or amendments in the booking at any time before service date must be dealt with us by calling at 8970000405/406 or write us at support@drivekool.com.
    * Booking amount you pay also includes 5% booking administration charges which are non-refundable in any case. 
    * All refunds will be strictly made of same credit card or bank account which was used to pay for booking.
    * Drivekool may take up to 2 weeks to process refunds for cancelled bookings following the above process. Your bank may debit its own separate charges from refunds made to your credit card or bank account. The amount would reflect in your account within the below mentioned timeline. 
      * 7-9 business days for Debit Card
      * 15 business days or in next billing statement for Credit card
      * 4-5 business days for Net-banking
    * Refund policy is applicable only when payment is made to drivekool. If you pay to driving schools directly then drivekool will not be responsible for refunding the amount in case of any issues. However drivekool will try to assist you getting you the refund. Drivekool also shall not refund money once it is transferred to driving school. 
**Drivekool's responsibilities** include:   

    * Issuing a valid enquiry for it's network of driving school operators
    * Providing customer support and information in case of any delays / inconvenience 
**Drivekool's responsibilities** do NOT include:  

    * The driving school operator’s driver not departing / reaching on time 
    * The driver employees being rude   

    * The driving service etc not being up to the students expectation
    * The baggage of the student getting lost / stolen / damaged while carrying during learning
    * The student waiting at the wrong boarding point (please call the driving operator to find out the exact boarding point)
  2. The arrival and departure times mentioned on the website are only tentative timings. However the driver will try to manage the time that is mentioned on the website.
  3. Students are required to furnish the following at the time of learning:-  
\- Identity proof (Driving license)   
Failing to do so, they may not be allowed to learn how to drive. 
  4. **Change of Vehicle :** In case the driving school operator changes the type of vehicle due to some reason, Drivekool is not responsible for above. 
  5. In case a confirmation e-mail and SMS gets delayed or fails because of technical reasons or as a result of incorrect e-mail ID / phone number provided by the student etc, However Drivekool will try to send confirmation e-mail and SMS within 1 hour to confirmation.

#### Communication Policy

  1. By accepting the terms and conditions, the student accepts that Drivekool may send the alerts to the mobile phone number provided by the student while enquiring for the service or to any such number replaced and informed by the student. The student acknowledges that the alerts will be received only if the mobile phone is in ‘On’ mode to receive the SMS. If the mobile phone is in ‘Off’’ mode then the student may not get / get after delay any alerts sent during such period. Drivekool will make best efforts to provide the service and it shall be deemed that the student shall have received the information sent from Drivekool as an alert on the mobile phone number provided during the course of booking and Drivekool shall not be under any obligation to confirm the authenticity of the person(s) receiving the alert. The student cannot hold Drivekool liable for non-availability of the service in any manner whatsoever 
  2. The student acknowledges that the SMS service provided by Drivekool is an additional facility provided for the student convenience and that it may be susceptible to error, omission and/ or inaccuracy. In the event the student observes any error in the information provided in the alert, Drivekool shall be immediately informed about the same by the student and Drivekool will make best possible efforts to rectify the error as early as possible. The student shall not hold Drivekool liable for any loss, damages, claim, expense including legal cost that may be incurred/ suffered by the student on account of the SMS facility.
  3. The student acknowledges that the clarity, readability, accuracy, and promptness of providing the service depend on many factors including the infrastructure, connectivity of the service provider. Drivekool shall not be responsible for any non-delivery, delayed delivery or distortion of the alert in any way whatsoever
  4. The student agrees to indemnify and hold harmless Drivekool and the SMS service provider including its officials from any damages, claims, demands, proceedings, loss, cost, charges and expenses whatsoever including legal charges and attorney fees which Drivekool and the SMS service provider may at any time incur, sustain, suffer or be put to as a consequence of or arising out of (i) misuse, improper or fraudulent information provided by the student, (ii) the student providing incorrect number or providing a number that belongs to that of an unrelated third party.
  5. . By accepting the terms and conditions, the student acknowledges and agrees that Drivekool may call the mobile phone number provided by the student while registering for the service or to any such number replaced and informed by the student, for the purpose of collecting feedback from the student regarding their learning, the driving facilities and/or services of the driving school.
  6. Grievances and claims related to the driving should be reported to Drivekool support team within 15 days of your learning.

#### Collection of Personally Identifiable Information and other Information

When you use our Website, we store your browsing information. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Website to make your experience safer and easier. More importantly, while doing so we collect personal information from you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

In general, you can browse the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website. We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our Website. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Website or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Website or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number.) from you when you set up a free account with us. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests.
